One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
The War's Conclusion
You've gotta be kidding me! What kind of doctor carries a sword around?!
Do you make house calls by submarine or something?!
What's wrong? Who is it?!
Trafalgar Law...
A rookie from the North Blue!
What?!
If I'm remembering right, he's a pirate who teamed up with Straw Hat Luffy and got away...
after the Celestial Dragon incident on the Sabaody Archipelago the other day!
It looks like they've come to save him in their submarine!
Don't waste any more time! Hand him over!
That's why I'm asking you who the hell you are and why I should trust you!
Captain Law! Warships are approaching off the stern!
Hurry! Bring both of them over here!
Calling all Navy soldiers!
Split into two forces:
push back the Whitebeard Pirates' attack,
and suppress the Blackbeard Pirates' ambush!
Marines are coming up from underground!
They had a path down there?!
We've got backup! All right! Take them out immediately!
W-What?!
What is this?!
What an extraordinary power!
I said I'll never let him escape!
You're not going anywhere!
He's putting on a pretty fantastic show, once again.
But I can't control it too well yet.
Hey, Captain! If you get too carried away, we'll lose our footing as well!
What do you think, Sengoku the Buddha?! Garp the Hero?!
Can you stop me?!
Your era ended with Whitebeard's!
What's Blackbeard doing now?!
I'm scared!
I've got a bad feeling about this!
Warning! Due to the earthquake that struck Marineford...
we are issuing a tsunami warning for the south coast of Sabaody Archipelago.
We assure you there is no cause for panic, please remain calm.
Please take shelter in the elevated areas of Groves 40 to 50, on the northern side of the archipelago.
Get out of the way! What are you waiting for?!
I'm a noble! I'll pay you, just let me go first!
Everyone, please remain calm.
The Pacifista have crossed the chasm in the plaza!
Follow the Pacifista! Don't let the pirates escape, men!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?!
I don't know! But I'm so sad!
Sad?
I can hear voices in my head...
disappearing, one by one...
What? Voices?
We'll show you Navy justice!
Is this your idea of justice?!
That's for my friend who died in the war!
Damn pirate! Go to Hell!
Now it's time to make them understand! The rulers of the sea are not the pirates, but us!
I did it!
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?!
Have you gone crazy? Get a hold of yourself!
H-Help me...
Run!
Koby!
Hey! Where are you going?!
As many of us must escape as possible!
Hang in there! You can still be saved!
We must get him treated!
I... I don't want to die...
Abandon him! We're at war here!
B-But Sir...
This is the time to show the power of the Navy... of justice!
We have no time to tend to the wounded!
Go!
Y-Yes Sir!
Chase down the pirates!
Kill every last one of them!
Someone, help him! Anyone!
Destroy the pirates! Don't leave a single one alive!
The killing won't stop... The marines have accomplished their goals, but are far more brutal now!
Our bullets don't work!
Chase them!
Damn villains!
Something is wrong... with our "justice" and "evil"...
Both sides are acting in their own self-interests.
Damn it!
Listen up, men! As long as you are marines...
you must never forgive the evil we know as pirates!
Nobody can stop me!
I'll destroy everything and swallow it up!
Just leave Straw Hat Luffy behind.
That's...
It's Kizaru!
Hurry and get them over here!
All right, I'll leave them with you, whoever you are!
Do what you can!
Catch them, Jean Bart!
All right! Good job!
Let's dive!
You did well to escape from me on Sabaody, Trafalgar Law...
He's horribly injured! Is he still alive?
Let's hurry!
Damn it!
Just give it up!
That's enough!
A marine?
Koby!
Stop, already! All this fighting, just end it!
What's with him?
S-Someone...
H-Help us...
We're throwing people's lives away!
Even though every single soldier has a family waiting for them to return!
Even though we've already accomplished our goal!
We keep chasing pirates who don't want to fight, drawing out a battle that should already be over...
and abandoning soldiers who could be saved if we treat their wounds now!
And still, we're sacrificing even more people!
What about the soldiers who will fall after this?!
Koby?!
We're making them look like idiots!
Huh? Who the hell are you?!
You've wasted several seconds of my time. The Navy has no use for soldiers who aren't righteous!
It's hopeless... I'm gonna die!
But... I said it! I said what I wanted to say!
I have no regrets!
You did well, young marine.
You risked your life to create a brief moment of courage...
for better or worse, that has greatly changed the fate of the world.
Hurry! Hurry and bring him inside!
Yes, Captain!
That's not gonna work.
Don't do anything, Kizaru.
Oh, my... Benn Beckman...
That's... that ship is...
Cast off!
What is...
one of the Four Emperors of the New World doing here?!
It's Red Hair Shanks!
I've come...
to end this war!
Red Hair...
The one who put Luffy on the path to become a pirate!
It's the Red Hair Pirates!
No way!
The skirmish between Emperors Kaido and Red Hair was just a few days ago in the New World!
He made it all the way here already?!
Sh-Shanks?!
W-What are you doing here?!
Buggy!
Y-Your straw hat?
Give it to Luffy.
Why do I have to do that?!
I had a treasure map I wanted to give you, too...
Really?!
Yeah. It leads to a great treasure trove!
Oh, come on!
That's way too good to be true! You think you can fool me with a story like that?
All right. I'll just give it to someone else, then.
Wha-?! Oh, crap, wait! I'll do it!
I'll give it to him right away!
Chief!
You haven't seen Luffy for ten years!
Don't you want to take a look at him?
Yeah...
Captain! This is dangerous!
I know it's rare to see one of the Four Emperors, but hurry and close the doors!
Sure.
You forgot this! Here, catch!
Something's flying towards us.
This is...
Captain! Hurry! Hurry up!
Sure!
I would like to see him, but...
I'm entrusting you with this hat.
Make sure you give it back one day...
once you've become a great pirate.
That's a promise, Luffy.
If we met now...
it would break our promise, wouldn't it...
Luffy?
This should be a fun operation.
Red Hair, you scum!
You let Dragon's son escape!
Ice Age!
He's after the submarine!
The water is freezing over!
His pulse is starting to stabilize.
What now?
This is an emergency! The ice is closing in on us!
We'll dive quickly!
Looks like we got away...
W-We're safe...
Yasakani Sacred Jewel!
W-What is it now?!
We've got to go deeper! To the ocean floor!
We'll get hit! We're definitely gonna get hit!
Hurry! Full speed ahead!
Damn it... They just won't give up!
He didn't hit them, did he?
Ace's brother! Jinbe!
If they're still alive now...
then they're really lucky.
We'll just have to give up on them for now...
Why is that warship sailing out alone?
You must hurry!
Follow the submarine!
Follow it? But it's at the bottom of the ocean!
I doubt it even survived the Admirals' attacks just now...
No. They are, without a doubt, alive.
Listen well!
As one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
I shall definitely chase down Straw Hat Luffy and finish him off!
Report this to the Navy!
Y-Yes Ma'am!
B-But where should we go?
Just advance!
She's crazy, yet so beautiful!
What did you say?!
You were lying about the treasure map?!
D-D-Damn you!
It was a spur of the moment thing, Buggy.
It's been a long time, huh?
W-What do you mean
"It's been a long time, huh?"
Don't forget that I still hold a grudge against you, Shanks!
About what?
Don't tell me you've forgotten!
If you hadn't shouted at me back then,
I wouldn't have lost that treasure map, nor would I have Devil Fruit powers!
Oh, that's what you meant?
Thanks for the great reaction.
I've always hated this side of you!
As soon as we were reunited you took advantage of me!
I don't care if you've come to end this war, or whatever...
I'm ready to start a one-on-one war with you right now!
Did you see that?
I saw it!
He's talking to Red Hair Shanks, one of the Four Emperors...
with that attitude!
Captain Buggy!
We will follow you...
forever!
All right, I got it. Don't get upset.
What was that?!
But wait a second...
as long as I'm with these guys, I can get off this island safely!
Red Hair...
Marco.
Don't continue this fight any longer.
Just pull back quietly.
Hawk-Eye!
Where are you going?!
I agreed to fight Whitebeard...
Fighting Red Hair was not part of the agreement.
I'm leaving.
If you keep on fighting...
both sides will suffer more pointless casualties.
If anybody still wants to fight...
then come! We will be your opponents!
What do you say, Teach?
No, Blackbeard!
Let's stop for now.
I got what I wanted.
It's still too soon for us to fight you guys.
Let's go, men!
Everyone...
for now...
please listen to what I have to say.
Here's the final news report...
Whitebeard. Ace.
Please leave their burial to us.
This war was broadcast all over the world.
Don't exploit their deaths more than you already have!
What selfish crap are you spouting?!
Holding their heads up to the world will be the symbol of our victory!
The Vice Admiral is right!
Are you trying to disgrace our victory?!
We won't obey the orders of a pirate!
Very well.
Fleet Admiral!
I'm fine with entrusting them to you, Red Hair.
But, Sir!
I will take the blame.
Sorry about this.
Tend to the wounds of the fallen!
This war...
is over!
Everyone who can move, help the medical staff!
Start with the ones who are heavily injured!
We can't suffer any more casualties on this battlefield!
And so...
the greatest battle since the curtain first rose on the Great Age of Pirates...
the great war of Marineford, came to an end.
Engraving its place in history.